+964-7706634056 yasser.rahmeh94@gmail.com 🔀 Erbil - Downtown

SUMMARY

I am a man with great motivation, ambition and expectations, as I believe in my experience in administration, marketing and communicating with beneficiaries and clients even from other cultures, so I have the desire to be an active member of your great company by working in this position. I am so sure that I can handle the required responsibilities and able to achieve any assigned task, cause I am hardworking with keen eye on details ^-*

EXPERIENCE

Marketing Manager 6/2017 - 5/2020

At ETC - Training And Education Center

Create unique marketing methods ,which increase the amount of revenue and make potential clients actual ones

1/2019 - 1/2020

warehouse management

At Hama Pharma

-Managing all input, output and inventory operations. -Coordination with the Sales, Purchasing and Accounting Department. -Commitment to the principle of cleanliness, safety and security.

1/2021 - 6/2021

Monitoring and Evaluation Program Supervisor

At UNDP (United Nations Development Programme)

Supervising the collection and renewal of data for families benefiting from the relief and humanitarian aid program

2/2020 - 12/2020

Reception And Reservation

At Al-Zaitona Hotel

Managing reservation systems, accounts and coordinating tourist groups in addition to foreign customers

QUALIFICATIONS

9/2016 - Present

Information Technology From Syrian Virtual University

10/2014 - 8/2016

Commerce & Economics (Banking & Financing)

From Tishreen University

SKILLS

Technical Skills



Management Skills

☑ Office Management

Project Management

Monitoring and Evaluation

LANGUAGES

English Expert

☑ Russian Intermediate

INTERESTS

Documentation Swimming

Music

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Father's Name Nationality

Khaled Syrian

Date Of Birth Marital Status

5/11/1994 Married

REFERENCES